ATEFEH ETEMADIPOUR

atefeh.etemadipour@gmail.com
Linkedin.com/in/atefeh-etemadipour-bb575a158
0793593574
Stockholm, Sweden

JUNIOR UX DESIGNER

With a background in industrial engineering and more than 4 years of sales experience, I'm eager to work in the field of product design. As an industrial engineer, I gained knowledge about creating products, and as a salesperson in the software sector, I had many close relationships with customers. In order to accomplish my goal, I enrolled in a UX Design course and began learning about it. I'm so excited about the new techniques and tools I've discovered and I like to apply them in real life products

SKILLS

- Figma (Software)
- Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity & High-Fidelity Prototypes
- Usability Testing
- User Stories and User Personas
- User-centered Design
- Miro Collaboration Platform
- Inkscape
- Microsoft office
- MSP
- Microsoft Dynamics CRM

EDUCATION

INDUSTRIAL ENGINEERING, BACHELOR(BSC/BA)

Sadjad Institute of Higher Education, Khorasan Razavi, Iran 2004 - 2009

Project: Production Scheduling using Invasive Weed Optimization Algorithm, using Python

EXPERIENCE

NOAVARAN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES GROUP IRAN, TEHRAN

Sales expert (Jun 2016 - Mar 2018) Salesperson in the sale department,

Extending the contract of organizations that are party to the contract and setting up the contract of new organizations
Telephone support of organizations

KIAN PARDAZ HOOSHMAND IRAN, TEHRAN

CRM specialist (Jun 2014 - Jun 2016)

CRM expert in the support and sale sector for Microsoft Dynamics CRM

Customizing Microsoft dynamics CRM

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

- FOUNDATION OF USER EXPERIENCE (UX) DESIGN -COURSERA
- START THE UX DESIGN PROCESS: EMPATHIZE, DEFINE AND IDEATE COURSERA
- BUILD WIREFRAMES AND LOW-FIDELITY PROTOTYPES COURSERA
- CREATE HIGH-FIDELITY DESIGNS AND PROTOTYPES IN FIGMA
- CONDUCT UX RESEARCH AND TEST EARLY CONCEPTS COURSERA
- PLANNING A CAREER IN USER EXPERIENCE LINKEDIN
- UX DESIGN: OVERVIEW LINKEDIN
- UX DESIGN: ANALYZING USER DATA LINKEDIN
- MSP INDUSTRILAL MANAGEMENT INSTITUTE IRAN-TEHRAN
- NETWORK+ CYBERTECH ACADEMY IRAN-TEHRAN

LANGUAGES

PERSIAN NATIVE ENGLISH FLUENT

SWEDISH SVAGRUND DELKURS 2